sanzarrugby.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Official SANZAR Site

#### SANZAR Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how SANZAR Pty Ltd uses and protects any information that you might give SANZAR when you use this website.

SANZAR is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

SANZAR may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 March 2011.

##### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

##### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
  * We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.
  * We may use the information to customise our website according to your interests.

##### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

##### Links to other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

In some circumstances, you may be entitled to gain access to the information SANZAR holds about you. If you wish to do so, please contact SANZAR in writing at email: [info@sanzarrugby.com](mailto:info@sanzarrugby.com)
